As we all travel across
the sea Raising our
voices We take in the beautiful blue world
Our spirits ready to go Everybody rejoices
Now let's go get the sails all unfurled
yeah yeah Here we are
in between the sea and
the sky Ready now for adventure We're itching
to try Get ready to roam So all aboard
now we're set to go Set sail to the ocean
so deep Ready for a truly grand adventure
Well don't you think that sounds really
fun All this excitement is second to none
As we all travel across
the sea Raising our
voices we take In the beautiful blue world
Our spirits ready to go Everybody rejoices
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled
If there's something that I just won't ever
forget It's the way that I felt when our
journey was set Now I won't be scared As
long as I keep that
feeling there With that,
let us keep up the pace While
enjoying every trip from place to
place Our timid hearts get the
rhythm ingrained So let's keep going,
adventure awaits So many treasures
await So now let's raise our voices
in pride Laughing out when they are
found With all the riches in hand,
everybody rejoices Party on,
cause we stand tall and proud
Life is adventurous, be aware it's
dangerous Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you now, fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
Don't stop, you can't die.
The damn thing's a zombie,
you'll get right back up.
You son of a...
Huh?
Hold on
You, I know you're from somewhere?
Never fear, I've got this under control!
You do?
Even the dead can be killed
if you know their weakness.
The hell is that thing?
That thing would be
the soul of the zombie.
It's soul.
Why is it coming out of his mouth?
No, captain.
Go on.
Get out of here.
Return to your rightful owner.
Captain Terraron!
He killed him!
He killed our captain!
Captain!
You obliterated the guy.
How'd you do that?
I purified him. Pure what?
It's him!
There's no doubt!
He's the humming swordsman!
He's the one who wreaked all that
destruction on Thriller Park five years ago.
We gotta report this to the master!
Oh, I know that web feels
like it's stronger than steel,
but you can melt right
through it with fire.
Really?
Well, I'll be damned, you're right!
Straw Hat and the rest of the
crew got captured, so let's talk.
You seem to know a lot about
this creepy island. I do.
It's just I'm not really sure.
How to say this but if your friends
have already been captured then
there's a very high probability
that it's too late to help them.
Hey? Wait!
What do you mean? Too late!
I can't bear to be such hostility!
But then again I am a skeleton.
So I don't have a face.
Skull joke!
Don't bother.
He's already dead, remember?
Anyhow, try to be serious
for a moment here.
I know he's annoying, but he's still dead.
I tried to explain this
while aboard the ship?
But there was a great deal
of time many years ago.
that I spent drifting aimlessly
about the sea, lost and all alone.
When I thought that I'd finally charted
my escape from this demonic sea,
my rudder broke and I was
cast even further into
the depths of this watery
void and then it happened!
I suppose it was about five years
ago much in the same way that it
happened to you the island of Thriller
Bark called out to me I was utterly
desperate to escape the Florian
triangle no matter the risk so I took a
chance and decided to scour the island
hunting for parts to fix the rudder.
All that was to be found on the island
was a horde of monsters and zombies.
It didn't take long before they captured
me and brought me to this building.
It was here that I witnessed
something incredible.
With me was a Kong fu dancer who had
also been captured some time before me.
They brought him before a stitched-up
corpse they referred to as a marionette.
Before I knew it, one of the most frightening
creatures I had ever seen appeared.
and then the dancer's shadow was ripped
right from his body and it was amputated.
how is that even possible
i could hardly believe
my eyes when i saw it
luckily i don't have eyes!
cut the crap i'm gonna beat
you up now that i can approve.
It didn't take him long to finish with
a dancer and move on to my shadow.
Once your shadow is taken, you
fall lifeless to the floor.
But the shadow remains active,
struggling up until the moment
it's confined within the corpse.
And once this act is complete,
I witness the marionette go from lifeless
meat to a full-blown dancing zombie!
You gonna explain this?
It's the shadows.
It doesn't matter whom
the corpse belongs to,
the shadows retain the characteristics
of the soul they originate from.
Of course, the shadow at
your feet is the same.
That reflection of your soul,
your other half, if you will, is intended
to follow you from birth until death.
Only one man possesses
the loathsome ability
to force those shadows to submit to him.
A member of the seven warlords
of the sea, Gecko Moria.
He's endowed with the power
of the shadow shadow fruit.
Devil Fruit powers.
The only materials needed to
make a zombie are a corpse
in the living shadow of
some unfortunate individual.
But the zombies, you see,
are not merely corpses,
but a collection of human and animal
parts stitched together by Dr.
Hawkback.
Merde is a brilliant accomplice.
He collects the corpses of legendary
warriors from around the world and,
using his medical expertise,
outfits their bodies with new parts.
And trust me, he's amassed
quite the collection.
A countless number of monstrosities stored
away in his lab and ready to live again.
Dr. Hogback, huh?
He was a well-renowned surgeon
who disappeared some time ago,
and to think he's been using his
skills to help a pirate ever since.
So, these zombies aren't really
resurrected from the dead.
They've just got somebody else's soul
working away inside their bodies.
Precisely.
The personality and fighting ability
comes from the Shadow's original owner,
but the physical strength is completely
dependent upon the corpse itself.
When these two elements are both powerful,
their combination creates
a truly formidable zombie.
Which is why Moria is so
eager to get his wicked
hands on those with ample
bounties on their head?
Well, that makes sense.
At least we know why we're being targeted
now I imagine one of the greatest
advantages for Moria is the absolute
obedience that zombies provide.
He needn't worry about winning the
favor of their original personalities.
A living army of such powerful fighters
would be too difficult
for anyone to control.
Indeed,
and since the shadows he takes have the
same abilities as their original owners,
then he has no need for the less
manageable bodies they were attached to.
The stronger they are, the faster he sends
them out to sea, before they wake up.
But that means we gotta find our guys.
They're alright for now,
there's still time to save them.
However, you must put your complete trust
in me if you want to accomplish that,
as my experience will have to serve
as your guide. What? Trust you?
Why should I?
Rejected! Skullsack!
It's been years since I've had such
an emotionally engaging conversation.
It's so much fun!
Are you going to tell
us what to do or not?
Sure.
Master Gloria!
Your three guests have
arrived, Master! They're early.
Shoo them in!
Right this way!
Welcome!
I'm glad you could make it.
Now hurry and make me king of the pirates!
Of course!
What'd you say about king of the pirates?
No one's gonna be king
of the pirates but me!
Now untie these damn ropes, you jerk!
Let me out of here!
Usopp, Nami, Chopper, Sanji,
Zoro, give me back my friends!
Where'd you put them, you big fat onion?
Quite an energetic fellow we've got here.
I take it this is Straw Hat Luffy.
Hey, you know what Straw Hat Luffy?
You just dropped a lot of names there.
But we've only caught three of
your guys so far, including you.
We've got Pirate Hunter Zoro,
and some lanky blonde guy who was with your
crew, but doesn't seem to have a bounty.
Who do I know with blonde
hair besides Sanji?
No way!
This is bad.
They caught Zoro and Sanji.
How's that possible?
They got them and Luffy?
No offense, but they're the
strongest guys on our crew.
How the hell were they the
first ones to get caught?
I don't know who any of these guys
are, but they are seriously dangerous.
That reminds me.
What happened to the three
you're in charge of Perona?
Huh?
I thought the Risky Brothers were
supposed to deliver them to us.
They're supposed to give them
to Kumasi, but they haven't yet.
Let's hope they didn't
escape during transit.
You hear that?
They're talking about us. Shut up!
Don't tell them, you bastard!
Didn't I tell you to keep your mouth shut?
You're too strict on Kumasi.
Unbearably strict, you might say.
Among these three, my bride-to-be
is the one to watch out for.
She caused a rebellion of sorts
in the middle of your garden.
Hey, hang on a second.
Damn it, hold back.
You, you better not have laid a single
sick finger on my bride, you bastard.
You bring her to me now.
Your bride doesn't want
you. What, Century?
What'd you say?
Hey, come on, Century.
You're not helping matters here.
And by the way, why do you always
stand in front of me like that?
She doesn't want you either
Your whining's giving me a headache
if those pirates somehow get away.
I hold every one of you responsible
I Gathered the three of you here
to commemorate the birth or rather
the rebirth of a powerful new
addition to the crew of Thriller Park?
He really is quite impressive.
Master the Pirate's escaping.
He ate right through the bars of the cage.
He did what now?
He ate the cage.
Let's just see you jerks
trying to catch me now.
Fast, fast, fast, fast, fast.
Such a promising shadow.
Hold on, Absalom.
We're in a tight space here.
Let me catch him, okay?
Yeah, I'd like to see you try, Slowpoke!
Like a damn hollow!
That's it.
I just want to die and be
reincarnated as a sea cucumber.
First he wants to be a pirate king,
then a knight, and now a sea cucumber?
Sad.
Let me go!
Let's illuminate our friend here.
What are you going to do, you jerk?
I'm going to make you pay!
What?
What the hell?
My shadow!
No! No!
Don't do it!
The shadow of a man with a 300
million fairy bounty is all mine!
Now we'll create the most powerful
special zombie the world has ever seen!
What?
Return to the ship?
You want us to go back on board the Sunny?
Yes, that's right.
If your comrades have been
captured, I fear the worst.
By now, and if not very soon, they will
have surely had their shadow stolen.
But even if that's the
case, they won't die.
Their bodies will likely
be taken back to your boat.
You see this?
They'll end up just like me.
Wait!
The shadow part, not the dead part!
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
Let's move on. Anyway,
like you were saying, even if you have
your shadow taken, you won't die, right?
Yes, that would be correct.
But whenever it's taken, you immediately
weaken and lose consciousness,
usually for about two days or so.
If the victim is strong enough,
then they'll put the bodies on a ship
and send them to drift out in the sea,
which is why I'm urging
you to return to yours.
Any guess as to why they do this?
Well,
I would assume it's to prevent the victims
from trying to take back their shadows,
correct?
Yes,
why don't they just kill them
while they're unconscious
and get it over with that's
something they cannot do
Now this is important.
So be sure to pay close attention
Firstly.
Even though the body and
shadow have been separated.
They still represent one
being think of the shadow as a
soul if the body dies the
shadow will disappear as well?
Thusly killing the host
zombie in the process
since they're trying to
build an army of minions.
This would certainly
not bode well for them
Secondly,
in the likely event that your friends
have had their shadows stolen,
they would most definitely
still be alive and their
bodies would be returned to
your ship as soon as possible.
Which is why the two of you must not
lose your shadows as well. If you do,
all hope will be lost
and you'll be forced to
wander these seas
aimlessly for all eternity.
While you have this window of opportunity,
you should use it to attempt
to awaken your comrades.
Once you do you must regroup and
formulate a plan to reclaim their shadows
Do you understand does all
of this make sense? Hmm?
Yeah, I think so your shadow story wasn't
so crazy after all both of you take this
What is it?
The weakness of these zombies hmm.
You've seen its power
This was the weapon I
used to defeat that spider
monkey their weakness, huh?
Huh?
What is this stuff, anyway?
It's ordinary salt.
It's just salt?
Not exactly what I had in mind
as the vanquisher of evil.
Does it lift a curse or something?
Well, I suppose that would be
one way of putting it, yes.
The reanimated life of these zombies is
brought about by a Devil Fruit power.
And just as one who is a power
holder is weakened by seawater,
the salt that is contained
in that water can also be
used as a weapon to unbind
the shadow from a zombie?
leaving them permanently deceased.
Okay, I get it.
And when this spider monkey went down,
that black thing that
floated out of him afterwards
was someone else's shadow
that he'd been given.
To think something so simple
would be their weakness.
So in summation, in order to defeat the
zombies, simply throw salt in their mouths.
That's the trick. Salt. Mouth.
Deader than dead.
Make no bother.
Pardon me, Brooke.
But how do you know so much about
this island and its residents?
And how do you know the zombies' weakness?
It all relates back to an incident
on this island five years ago.
The time when I lost my shadow.
I was sent out to sea.
Just like all the others.
Luckily I awoke and was
able to retrace my path.
And return here.
Once I did.
I went ashore and began my battle.
I fought against
The very zombie that had my shadow.
Unfortunately, the outcome
was a crushing defeat.
Because I vowed to survive
no matter what I faced.
I ran.
Even if it was shameful,
I had to keep on living.
I have an obligation, you see.
I was the only survivor of my crew.
One day, I will escape these evil seas.
and make good on the promises
made by myself and my comrades.
Until then, I cannot die a second time.
Sadly, living longer hasn't helped me to
keep my promises or reach my goal at all.
But this time, I'm back
and I won't run away!
Not until I defeat that
man and reclaim my shadow!
I'm in a hurry, so please excuse me.
I'll be on my way now.
Good luck to you.
Hold on a second!
While you're still in a mood to talk,
there's one more burning question
I still need an answer to.
Poor Luffy!
What just happened?
That's not possible. Is it?
His shadow!
He cut it off and took it!
Wait a minute.
We've heard about this, haven't we?
Didn't that skeleton say the
same thing happened to him?
Yeah, I remember he said
his shadow was stolen.
Then this must be the guy that did it.
I bet you're right.
How awful.
What's the trick?
It must be a Devil Fruit power.
Promise it. Listen, you.
Don't make me keep repeating
myself over and over again.
You're not the least bit cute
when you talk, so don't do it.
This little guy is just
what I need to bring me
one step closer to becoming
king of the pirates.
Right, Doctor Hawkback.
Since the time I met you ten years ago.
I've put all my time, resources,
and energy into making number 900.
With that shadow, it will make
the greatest zombie of all time.
With that power at your fingertips,
nothing will be beyond your reach.
That means it will only
be a matter of time.
Before I become the
cemetery king of the entire
world and I'll transform
all the cute creatures of
the world into zombies
then I'll have an entire
adorable kingdom full of
servants that never talk back.
That's right.
It doesn't matter who the person is,
how powerful they are or how
strong-willed they may be.
Once their shadow is taken and placed
in another, they bow to your will.
Soon I'll fill the world with my servants.
If I'd had an army like that
before, I wouldn't have been.
beaten by that idiot
Kaido in the new world.
I think it's about time we
open his eyes, don't you?
Yoro, Nien, bow! Yes,
Master! What's your command?
Go on ahead and open the door
to the special refrigerator.
Right!
As you wish, Master!
It's almost time, sweet 900.
In but a few moments, your
eyes will open at last.
The perfect shadow has finally
found its way to my doorstep.
Spider-Mouse, come here!
Yes!
Take Straw Hat Luffy's body
and throw it back on his ship.
Make sure to remove those webs.
We'll be in trouble if he dies.
Look at him!
Wait, I have an urgent report to give you!
What is it?
Just moments ago, the spider monkey
Captain Tararon was defeated by intruders!
Defeated?
Huh, what does that matter as
long as his shadow wasn't removed?
But that's just it!
His shadow was removed!
You're certain of this?
Yes, there's no doubt!
Team Absalom!
Only one man is capable of doing this!
He has returned!
Damn that humming swordsman!
It seems the reports I received this
morning weren't so crazy after all.
How could this happen?
The humming swordsman is running around
removing every zombie
shadow he comes across!
Out of nowhere, the number of
casualties has gone through the roof!
Everything's playing out just like the
terrible ordeal we went
through five years ago!
That swordsman!
That damned humming swordsman! Bastard!
That infuriating troublemaker
is the only enemy
we have that knows the
weakness of the zombies.
How did he manage to return here again?
And what is she doing?
How much damage has he managed to
do this time? Shandora! Stop that!
Why do you keep blocking me?
The Humming Swordsman.
I've heard many stories about him,
but just what kind of a man is he?
You don't mean that you've...
Perona, are you saying you've
never seen his face before?
I see then.
That's probably how he slipped
past your ghost network undetected.
Yeah, so it would seem.
Master, apparently that humming
pain in the ass has returned.
Like I care.
Don't bother me with such nonsense, idiot.
I'm busy.
You take care of it.
Hold on!
Come on, let's make our
way to the refrigerator.
Master, I have news concerning
the current situation.
Why didn't you say so before?
Cool!
If that's the case, slowing
him down shouldn't be an issue.
Keep me informed of any more
problems should they arise!
Now hurry up and dump
Straw Hat on the boat!
Idiot!
Keep quiet!
He lost his shadow!
That doesn't mean he's dead!
Remember Brooke said so.
Kumasi! Hurry up!
We can't just hop out right now!
Wait for the right moment!
It sounds like they have
plans for Luffy's shadow.
We need to keep hiding
in here to find out where
they're taking it so
we can rescue it later!
To think that Tararan
was defeated. Impressive.
More importantly, where is the enemy?
I must find them and slice them!
Listen, Franky.
What is it?
You're wrong, I'm not crying!
I'm not crying, you punk!
Stop looking at me already!
I wanted to know.
Why did you ask him about that?
Leave me alone!
I have my reasons, okay?
Ah, damn it!
I can't help it!
I love that damn skeleton!
He's the nicest guy in the whole world!
It's not fair!
That's true.
You just don't know when to quit, do you?
I'll never quit!
Don't you remember who I am?
Men cower in fear at the mere mention
of the Swordmaster Ryuma Silence!
You're nothing more than my shadow
Yet my body is much stronger.
I'll return you to where
you belong, beneath my feet!
I'm looking forward to this.
When I first came across this corpse in
the Land of Ice, I couldn't stop shaking.
Honestly, I was trembling.
It's simply fascinating to think that such
a monstrous creature
was alive and breathing?
wreaking havoc across
the seas 500 years ago.
The countries that fell at
his hands were taken whole.
Under his strength, a legendary
nation of criminals was born.
Imagine my surprise when
I found myself staring
at the demon they called
the continent below.
Man, it keeps getting colder and colder.
Where in the world were
these guys going anyway?
I have no idea,
but they said something earlier about
some sort of special refrigerator,
didn't they?
I can't believe I'm going to
revive this extraordinary creature.
This will go down in the
books of zombie creationists.
Century, why do you keep blocking me?
Another legend will be
brought back to life.
The time for his revival is finally here.
Behold, the only warrior in history
who was ruthless and powerful
enough to be given the name Devil.
This is Oz.
Thank you.